{
    "id": "da5e700bb299492f84818eb52fa2d056",
    "title": "No, Not Or None",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d3b37e9727f8440ba13c89dc008c8d52",
            "title": "No, Not And None",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have ......................... time to talk to you now.",
                    "description": "No is used with a noun to mean not any.",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has answered ................................ of the questions.",
                    "description": "We use none of before a pronoun or a noun with a determiner. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "none",
                        "no one"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................. matter what you say, I won't believe you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "None",
                        "No one"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ............................. fool.",
                    "description": "This is a more emphatic way of saying 'She is not a fool.'",
                    "answers": [
                        "not",
                        "no",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. of the students participated in the program.",
                    "description": "We use none of before a noun with a determiner. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "None",
                        "No",
                        "Not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .............................. longer support the liberals.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not",
                        "no",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I waited for hours, but .............................. came.",
                    "description": "No one means the same as nobody.",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "no one",
                        "not one"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. of them could solve the puzzle.",
                    "description": "We use none of before a pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "No one",
                        "None"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................. surprisingly, he failed the test.",
                    "description": "We use not to make a word, clause or expression negative. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "Not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can come tomorrow, but ................................ on Monday.",
                    "description": "We use not to make a word, clause or expression negative. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "no",
                        "not",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ of the onlookers came forward to help him.",
                    "description": "We use none of before a pronoun or a noun with a determiner. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "None",
                        "Not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... doctors went on strike.",
                    "description": "No is used with a noun to mean not any.",
                    "answers": [
                        "No",
                        "Not",
                        "None"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}